theonlineticketshop.com 2009-06-05

# The Online Ticket Shop: Privacy Policy.

**Welcome to the Privacy Policy for TheOnlineTicketShop.com ("Privacy Policy").** The services available at [http://www.TheOnlineTicketshop.com](http://www.theonlineticketshop.com/)?are provided by **TheOnlineTicketExchange.COM LIMITED** ("TheOnlineTicketExchange", "we", "us" or "our"), company number 6492553 whose registered office is at 85-87 Borough High Street, London, SE1 1NH United Kingdom. 

Your privacy is very important to us. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. If you have additional questions about TheOnlineTIcketShop.com's general privacy principles, please either read the pages at our Privacy Central section available or contact [ inforeq@theonlineticketshop.com](mailto:inforeq@theonlineticketshop.com). 

Overview   
By accepting this Privacy Policy and the User Agreement, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. If you object to this use and disclosure please do not register with us. 

This Privacy Policy contains a number of references to other pages on our Site and other websites. Please note: underlined words and phrases are click-through links to these pages and websites. TheOnlineTIcketShop.com strongly recommends that you click on such links to obtain further important details about the Privacy Policy, as they may contain further terms and conditions which apply to you as an TheOnlineTIcketShop.com member. 

This Privacy Policy applies to the http://www.TheOnlineTIcketShop.com website (the "Site"). 

###  An Important Note about Children. 

Our services are not available to children and we ask that persons under the age of 18 do not submit any personal information to us. If you are under 18 years old, you can use this service only in conjunction with and under the supervision of a parent or guardian. 

###  Information We Collect. 

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, efficient, and personalised experience.   
In general, you can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to use our services, we may require you to provide contact and identity information, financial information and other personal information as indicated on the forms throughout the Site. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. 

You always have the option not to provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature.   
Under some circumstances we may require some additional financial information, such as, but not limited to, credit card details if you are registering using an email account at certain email services, or registering to buy tickets from the Site. We use this financial information to help verify your name, address, and other information. We may also use this information to charge you for your use of our services. 

We automatically collect and process certain information based upon your use of the Site. We use this information to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, serve and protect you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Site or not), browser information, and your IP address. 

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Site. "Cookies" are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customised services and to help promote safer trading. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently while you are using the Site. Cookies can also help us provide information which we tailor to your interests. Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session using the Site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently while you are using the Site. 

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Site that are placed by third parties. For example, if you view a web page created by a user, there may be a "cookie" placed within that web page. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

If you choose to buy on the Site, we collect information about your buying behaviour. 

If you establish a credit account with us to pay the fees we charge, we collect some additional information, including but not limited to a billing address, a credit card number and a credit card expiration date. 

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. 

If you register for TheOnlineTIcketShop.com (a) on another web site, or (b) use a web site providing a service for TheOnlineTIcketShop.com, or (c) a web site that helps facilitate your activity on TheOnlineTIcketShop.com, that web site may provide personal information about you and your transactions back to TheOnlineTIcketShop.com. 

###  Our Use of Your Information. 

We use information in the files we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to resolve disputes, provide customer support, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement and policies. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes, and in particular we may examine your information to identify users using multiple User IDs or aliases. 

You agree that we may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customise the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs. 

You agree that we may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banner advertisements, administrative notices, product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. By accepting the User Agreement and reading this Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive this information. If you do not wish to receive these communications, please notify us by email to inforeq@theonlineticketshop.com 

###  Our Disclosure of Your Information. 

TheOnlineTicketShop.com MAY USE YOUR INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE AS DETERMINED IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION. Without limiting the foregoing, we may share or sell your personally identifiable information with third parties for their direct and online marketing purposes. Though we are selective as to the identities of these third parties and endeavour to work with entities with similar policies and practices, we do not control the policies and practices of these third parties, and it is possible that they will use your information in a manner which is inconsistent with this privacy policy, and they may not provide the opportunity to opt-out or unsubscribe from their service.

We may enhance or merge your personally identifiable information with data collected from other sources to use in direct or online marketing, including the data services described on the Site. All information provided to us may be used to support our marketing and data services businesses. These services include the provision of and use of personally identifiable data to marketing companies, advertising agencies, data compilers, data companies, and, to the extent permitted by law, individual reference and look-up service programs. 

We send e-mail to individuals who have agreed on the Site to receive e-mail from us or to individuals who have agreed on third party websites to receive e-mail from third parties such as us. As a result, laws requiring particular information or certain formatting for unsolicited commercial e-mail are not applicable to our messages.

TheOnlineTicketShop.com cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties, to enforce laws and third party rights, such as intellectual property rights and laws relating to fraud. Therefore, in response to a verified request by law enforcement or other government officials such as a Section 29 (3) Data Protection Act 1998 form relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity, or other activity that may expose us or you to legal liability, we can (and you authorise us to) disclose personal information such as name, address, telephone number, email address, User ID history and listing history about you as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. 

###  Control of Your Password. 

You are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password, including those actions that result in fees being charged to your account. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your TheOnlineTicketShop.com password to any third parties. If you choose to share your User ID and password or your information with third parties where it is necessary for you to do so for them to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your User ID and password and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password or account has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password as detailed below. 

###  Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information. 

You can change your User ID, password, contact information, financial information, postal address and user preferences by emailing us at inforeq@theonlineticketshop.com.

You must promptly notify us if your personal information changes or is inaccurate.

Upon your written request, we will deactivate your account, contact information, and financial information from our active databases. To make this request, please contact inforeq@theonlineticketshop.com. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law. 

We will retain in our files information you have requested us to remove in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes & troubleshoot problems. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored "back up" systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests. 

###  Other Information Collectors. 

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are buyers or sellers on the Site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since TheOnlineTicketShop.com does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

### Security.

TheOnlineTicketShop.com uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including encryption, "firewalls" and Secure Socket Layers. TheOnlineTicketShop.com treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorised access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorised access by users inside and outside the company. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

###  Notice. 

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time in order that it accurately reflects the regulatory environment and our own data collection and disclosure practices. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. In addition, we will notify you by posting the amended Privacy Policy on the Site.
